Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: Road to the pyramids - westward toward Gizeh from a point near Cairo, Egypt: We have crossed the river Nile from Cairo, leaving the city behind us, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44-verso (Box 1608)
  - Great Sphinx of Gizeh, the largest royal portrait ever hewn, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Great Sphinx of Gizeh, the largest royal portrait ever hewn, Egypt: We are standing with our backs to the great Nile river, looking west, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45-verso (Box 1608)
  - Looking up an angle of the Great Pyramid, showing the difficulties of its Ascent, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Looking up an angle of the Great Pyramid, showing the difficulties of its Ascent, Egypt: From our point of view, the vast mass of this hoary monument seems almost to overwhelm us, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46-verso (Box 1608)
  - Inundation of the Nile, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Inundation of the Nile, Egypt: The wonders of ancient Egypt are in the scene before you, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47-verso (Box 1608)
  - The palms of Memphis on the site where once stood a mighty city, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The palms of Memphis on the site where once stood a mighty city, Egypt: Twelve miles due south of Cairo stood Memphis, one of the most famous cities of ancient times, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48-verso (Box 1608)
  - Egyptian Fellahin lifting water from the Nile, with Shadoofs, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Egyptian Fellahin lifting water from the Nile, with Shadoofs, Egypt: Bronzed laborers still work the dark, alluvial soil with primitive instruments, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49-verso (Box 1608)
  - Where primitive methods still prevail - threshing beans in Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Where primitive methods still prevail - threshing beans in Egypt: "Thou shalt not muzzle the ox when he thresheth", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50-verso (Box 1608)
  - The magnificent desolation of the desserted temple of Luxer, southwest from the First Pylon, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The magnificent desolation of the desserted temple of Luxer, southwest from the First Pylon, Egypt: What would have been the thought of the proud conquerors of the eigteenth dynasty, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51-verso (Box 1608)
  - Tomb of King Tutankhamun, Valley of the Kings, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Tomb of King Tutankhamun, Valley of the Kings, Egypt: Before us in the wild and desolate valley of Biban-el-Muluk, lies the tomb of Tutankhamun, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52-verso (Box 1608)
  - Philae the "Pearl of Egypt," now submerged by waters stored by Assuan Dam, Egypt, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Philae the "Pearl of Egypt," now submerged by waters stored by Assuan Dam, Egypt: This once beautiful island lies in the Nile just beow the first cataract, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53-verso (Box 1608)
  - Sisal hemp plantation in Blossom, Uganda, Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Sisal hemp plantation in Blossom, Uganda, Africa: This looks like a forest of young pines, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Native Market at Port Florence, Lake Victoria Nyanza, Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Native Market at Port Florence, Lake Victoria Nyanza, Africa: This scene is near the northern sohre of Victoria Nyanza at the western terminus of the Uganda Railway, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55-verso (Box 1608)
  - Ivory on the way from the jungle to America, Main Street, Mombasa, East Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Ivory on the way from the jungle to America, Main Street, Mombasa, East Africa: It is almost equatorial sunshine that ours down into this narrow street, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56-verso (Box 1608)
  - House-bulding by Masai women, their husbands looking on - East Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: House-bulding by Masai women, their husbands looking on - East Africa: We are in one of several villages in that part of East Africa which was a German colony, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57-verso (Box 1608)
  - Turumu Village and people in a forest clearing near Yakusa, Congo, Free State, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Turumu Village and people in a forest clearing near Yakusa, Congo, Free State: The Dark Continent, as Africa has been called, has been for centuries a land of mystery, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58-verso (Box 1608)
  - Climbing through a tropical jungle, Central Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Climbing through a tropical jungle, Central Africa: This outlook is in Central Africa, near the line of the equator, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59-verso (Box 1608)
  - Victoria Falls making a 343-foot plunge, Rhodesia, South Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Victoria Falls making a 343-foot plunge, Rhodesia, South Africa: Whether the Victoria Falls of Niagara are the finest in the world is a matter of opinion, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60-verso (Box 1608)
  - Heavy freight wagons crossing the Vaal River, South Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Heavy freight wagons crossing the Vaal River, South Africa: The Vaal River, rising in the mountainous district of Ermelo in the Transvaal, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61-verso (Box 1608)
  - Diamond mining, Kimberley, S. Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Diamond mining, Kimberley, S. Africa: An ostrich hunter, in 1869, by accident came across a few diamonds that had been found near the Vaal River, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62-verso (Box 1608)
  - Arrival of fishing boats at Cape Town, Union of South Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Arrival of fishing boats at Cape Town, Union of South Africa: Cape town is the metropolis of South Africa, a modern, thriving city of some 200,000 inhabitants, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63-verso (Box 1608)
  - Groot Schuur, the country home of Cecil Rhodes, Cape Town, S. Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Groot Schuur, the country home of Cecil Rhodes, Cape Town, S. Africa: Cecil John Rhodes was a very remarkable Englishman, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64-verso (Box 1608)
  - South African gannets in countless numbers, near Cape Town, South Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: South African gannets in countless numbers, near Cape Town, South Africa: A glance at this scene might lead one to believe that he was looking over a lake, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65-verso (Box 1608)
  - Penguins on Dassen Island near Cape Town, South Africa, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Penguins on Dassen Island near Cape Town, South Africa: A small island lying 40 miles north of Cape Town and six or eight miles from the mainland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66-verso (Box 1608)
  - Hauling snow for water supply, Belgica Antarctic Expedition, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Hauling snow for water supply, Belgica Antarctic Expedition: When Rome flourished on the Mediterranean the known world was limited to parts of three continents, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67-verso (Box 1608)
  - Roald Amundsen, Discoverer of the South Pole, Inspecting ice field near glacier, Antarctic Ocean, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Roald Amundsen, Discoverer of the South Pole, Inspecting ice field near glacier, Antarctic Ocean: This is a remarkable photograph of Roald Amundsen, discoverer of the South Pole, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68-verso (Box 1608)
  - A caravan of camels in the narrow road approaching Jaffa, Palestine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: A caravan of camels in the narrow road approaching Jaffa, Palestine: Jaffa, the gateway to the Holy Land, is full of geographic interest, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69-verso (Box 1608)
  - Garden of Gethsemane and Mount of Olives, from the Golden Gate, Jerusalem, Palestine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Garden of Gethsemane and Mount of Olives, from the Golden Gate, Jerusalem, Palestine: We are standing by the eastern wall of the hill-top city and looking east across the valley, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70-verso (Box 1608)
  - Jerusalem the city of the Great King, from the Mount of Olives, Palestine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Jerusalem the city of the Great King, from the Mount of Olives, Palestine: Looking down from the brow of Olivet, we see Jerusalem, "the City of the Great King", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71-verso (Box 1608)
  - Garden of Gethsemane (from North) and New Church, Jerusalem, Palestine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Garden of Gethsemane (from North) and New Church, Jerusalem, Palestine: We have entered now one of the most sacred spots in Christendom, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72-verso (Box 1608)
  - Christian Street, motley life in the Holy City's bazaar district, Jerusalem, Palestine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Christian Street, motley life in the Holy City's bazaar district, Jerusalem, Palestine: We are in the western part of the old city, facing north, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73-verso (Box 1608)
  - Rumanian mother and children, Orsova, Rumania, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Rumanian mother and children, Orsova, Rumania: Orsova is a city in the Transylvanian Alps, on the Danube River just above the famous Iron Gate, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74-verso (Box 1608)
  - In the market place of Serajevo, Jugoslavia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: In the market place of Serajevo, Jugoslavia: It is an evil fame that rests forever upon the little city whose market place we see.., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75-verso (Box 1608)
  - Market scene in Berkovitza, Bulgaria, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Market scene in Berkovitza, Bulgaria: One must arise early to be first at the market place of a Bulgarian village on market day, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76-verso (Box 1608)
  - Street scene, showing peasant woman and sidewalk coffee house, Sofia, Bulgaria, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Street scene, showing peasant woman and sidewalk coffee house, Sofia, Bulgaria: The captial of Bulgaria is Sofia, a city of considerably over 100,000 inhabitants, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77-verso (Box 1608)
  - Country circus troupe with dancing bear from Balkans, on Turkish Road, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Country circus troupe with dancing bear from Balkans, on Turkish Road: Theaters, vaudeville shows and moving pictures are popular in Constantinople, though they can have nothing like the large attendance, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78-verso (Box 1608)
  - Beautiful Constantinople, city of two continents - Asia in distance to the northeast (right), circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Beautiful Constantinople, city of two continents - Asia in distance to the northeast (right): The Asiatic city, known as Scutari, is out of sight northeast across the Bosphorus to the right, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79-verso (Box 1608)
  - St. Sophia, once Christian cathedral of Byzantium, now Mohammedan Mosque, Constantinople, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: St. Sophia, once Christian cathedral of Byzantium, now Mohammedan Mosque, Constantinople: We are in the oldest part of the oldest quarter of Constantinople, the southeast section of Stamboul near Seraglio Point, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80-verso (Box 1608)
  - Mohammedans at Prayer in the Mosque of St. Sophia, Constantinople, Turkey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Mohammedans at Prayer in the Mosque of St. Sophia, Constantinople, Turkey: We see only the central part of a vast and splendid building, constructed nearly fourteen centuries ago by the Roman emperor Justinian, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81-verso (Box 1608)
  - A Turkish meat market in Constantinople, Turkey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: A turkish meat market in Constantinople, Turkey: A polyglot mixture of races with a diversity of language and faiths is found in Constantinople, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82-verso (Box 1608)
  - A glimpse of two continents - Castle Rumill Hissar, the Bosporous and the Asiatic Shore from the European side, Constantinople, Turkey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: A glimpse of two continents - Castle Rumill Hissar, the Bosporous and the Asiatic Shore from the European side, Constantinople, Turkey :Probably no other city has ever appealed so strongly, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83-verso (Box 1608)
  - North over Pharsalia, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: North over Pharsalia, Greece: Greece is a farming country, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84-verso (Box 1608)
  - Southwest from the Lykabettos past Royal Palace and Acropolis to sea, Athens, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Southwest from the Lykabettos past Royal Palace and Acropolis to sea, Athens, Greece: That great marble building at our left is the palace of the king; rising in the middle distance is the ancient Acropolis, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85-verso (Box 1608)
  - Splendid columns of Temple of Olympian Zeus and the Acropolis in the distance, Athens, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Splendid columns of Temple of Olympian Zeus and the Acropolis in the distance, Athens, Greece: We are at the extreme southeastern edge of Athens, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86-verso (Box 1608)
  - Modern ship canal, first projected by Nero, through the Isthmus of Corinth, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Modern ship canal, first projected by Nero, through the Isthmus of Corinth, Greece: The position of ancient Corinth, built on the isthmus between northern Greece and the Peloponnesus, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87-verso (Box 1608)
  - Excavators at work, Old Corinth, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Excavators at work, Old Corinth, Greece: Greece is chiefly a peninsula extending into the Mediterranean Sea, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88-verso (Box 1608)
  - West to the Heights of Taygetus - looking over modern homes in Ancient Sparta, Greece, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: West to the Heights of Taygetus - looking over modern homes in Ancient Sparta, Greece: We are in the southern Peloponnesus, looking westward over part of Sparta, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89-verso (Box 1608)
  - Picking lemons in a grove of that Conea d'Oro (Golden Shell) near Palermo, Sicily, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Picking lemons in a grove of that Conea d'Oro (Golden Shell) near Palermo, Sicily: We are about two miles west of Palermo between the city and Monreale, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90-verso (Box 1608)
  - Goats milked while you wait - a crowded market place in Palermo, Sicily, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Goats milked while you wait - a crowded market place in Palermo, Sicily: Palermo, the capital of Sicily, is on the north coast of that island, on the gulf of Palermo, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91-verso (Box 1608)
  - The beautiful bay and city of Naples under the shadow of Mount Vesuvius, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The beautiful bay and city of Naples under the shadow of Mount Vesuvius, Italy: Our point of observation is on the balcony of an old monastery on a hill in the western part of town, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92-verso (Box 1608)
  - Wash day in a towering house of the old town, Naples, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Wash day in a towering house of the old town, Naples, Italy: Naples, the most densely populated city of Europe, has long been noted for its beauty and charm, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93-verso (Box 1608)
  - St. Peter's, the greatest of churches, Rome, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: St. Peter's, the greatest of churches, Rome, Italy: We have come to the top story of a fairly high house and are facing the great square of St. Peter's, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Library of the Vatican, one of the 1000 rooms in the Great Papal Palace, Rome, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Library of the Vatican, one of the 1000 rooms in the Great Papal Palace, Rome, Italy: It was Pope Sixtus who gave to Domenico Fontana the commission to construct the gorgeous repository, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Eternal City from the Dome of St. Peter's, Rome, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Eternal City from the Dome of St. Peter's, Rome, Italy: We are in the dome of the largest Christian church in the world, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Tiber, Castle of Saint Angelo and St. Peter's, the greatest church in Christiandom, Rome, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Tiber, Castle of Saint Angelo and St. Peter's, the greatest church in Christiandom, Rome: This is one of the most picturesque and comprehensive views in the city of Rome, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97-verso (Box 1608)
  - Gallery in Palace of the Colonna Family, Rome, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: Gallery in Palace of the Colonna Family, Rome, Italy: The huge Colonna palace has stood for centuries among the conspicuous edifices of the Eternal City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Forum where once centered the power and glory of Ancient Rome, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Forum where once centered the power and glory of Ancient Rome, Italy: The structures of the Forum, situated at the foor of Capitoline Hill, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99-verso (Box 1608)
  - The Leaning Tower and Eleventh Century Cathedral, Pisa, Italy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100 (Box 1608)
  - Verso: The Leaning Tower and Eleventh Century Cathedral, Pisa, Italy: The group of buildings before us is one of the most celebrated in all Europe, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100-verso (Box 1608)
  Box 1609
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Bethlehem of Judea, the Birthplace of Jesus-West from Church of Nativity, Palestine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Bethlehem of Judea, the Birthplace of Jesus, Palestine: If we will accept the authority of tradition, which in this case is probably true, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1-verso (Box 1609)
  - Pilgrims Receiving Baptism in the River Jordan, Palestine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Baptism of Pilgrims in the River Jordan, Palestine: Not only for its influence upon Biblical history, but because of many of its natural, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2-verso (Box 1609)
  - Samaria. Once Proud and Beautiful Center of the Northern Kingdom. Seen from the South, Palestine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Samaria Seen from the South, Palestine: Looking northward across the valley dotted with olive-trees, we see the once palatial city..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Home of the Child Jesus-Nazareth, Palestine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Home of the Child Jesus-Nazareth, Palestine: Half way between the Mediterranean and the Sea of Galilee, and sixty-five miles from, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4-verso (Box 1609)
  - Tiberias, a Town of Jewish Fishermen, Sea of Galilee, Palestine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Tiberias, a Town of Jewish Fishermen, Sea of Galilee, Palestine: Here is Tiberias, on the shore of the lake. This town was founded in the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5-verso (Box 1609)
  - General view of Damascus, Perhaps the World's Oldest Inhabited City, Syria., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Bird's-Eye View of Damascus, Syria: There is much to support the claim that Damascus is the most ancient city of the world which is, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6-verso (Box 1609)
  - Where Tradition Locates the Garden of Eden-Valley of the Euphrates, 250 Miles N. W. of Babylon, Iraq., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Where Tradition Locates the Garden of Eden: We are on the right bank of the Euphrates, facing east. Persia and Afghanistan and northern, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7-verso (Box 1609)
  - Picturesque Homes of Wealthy Jews along the Tigris in North Bagdad, Iraq., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Homes of Wealthy Jews Along Tigris in North Bagdad, Irak, Mesopotamia: Here we have a glimpse of domestic life in Bagdad, that once, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8-verso (Box 1609)
  - Throngs of Moslems and Jews in the Principal Street of Bagdad, Iraq., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Moslems and Jews in Street of Bagdad, Irak, Mesopotamia: We are strolling along the principal street of Bagdad, a city of 150,000 situated, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9-verso (Box 1609)
  - Palace of Nebuchadnezzar (6th Century B.C.) and Desolate Ruins of Once Mighty Babylon, Iraq., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Palace of Nebuchadnezzar and Ruins of Once Mighty Babylon: We are near the Euphrates river, between four and five hundred miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10-verso (Box 1609)
  - An Arab Village of Reed Mats, and Round Fort on Lower Euphrates, Iraq., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Arab Village of Reed Mats and Round Fort on Lower Euphrates: The traveler is on historic ground as he halts before this picturesque, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11-verso (Box 1609)
  - Parsees Worshipping before the New Moon, Bombay, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Parsees Worshipping before the New Moon, Bombay, India: The waters of the Indian Ocean are just behind us at the west: We are facing, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12-verso (Box 1609)
  - Sunset on an Orient Sea, off Ceylon, the "Pearl-drop on the brow of India.", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Sunset on an Orient Sea, off Ceylon: We are on the west coast of the island of Ceylon, a British colony, looking west across the great, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13-verso (Box 1609)
  - Curious Roots and Trunk of the India-rubber Tree, Peradeniya, Gardens, near Kandy, Ceylon., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: India-Rubber Tree, Peradeniya Gardens, near Kandy Ceylon: You are within the wonderful 150-acre enclosure of the Royal Botanic Gardens, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Few of India's Poverty-stricken Millions Characteristic Street in Madura, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Characteristic Street in Madura, India: Madura is the capital of a district in Madras. It is 270 miles southwest of Madras and about 125 miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15-verso (Box 1609)
  - Law Court Buildings and Substantial Elegance of the Modern City from the Bank, Madras, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Law Court Buildings and Modern Madras from Bank, India: It is the Indian Ocean whose waters you see over there beyond the domed, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16-verso (Box 1609)
  - Sacred Monkeys at Galta, near Jeypore, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Sacred Monkeys at Galta, near Jeypore, India: The rocky slope on which you are standing is the side of a mountain a mile and a half, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Taj Mahal, Agra, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18 (Box 1609)